I'll just give these away to anybody who
wants them. When you rent property, the
phrase one man's trash is another man's
treasure Oh, definitely holds
true.
The tenants said they moved out. Does
this look moved out to you? This is
actually one of my favorite rental
pastimes.
We call it homeless finds when you get
to go in here and see what they left.
Air pump? It's kind of like redneck
Christmas. That's like an $80 tape
measure. Do we need Lysol? You never
know when you got to measure 300 ft.
Yes, we do.
Boxes of herbs. What is that? A
solar-powered lantern. A [music] belly
button shaper?
>> Maintain the physique of your belly
button. That's a tortilla presser.
>> Yes.
Oh, a Strong's Concordance.
A topical Bible for no-time Bible study.
You're mapping out a bus build, Alex. I
wonder if this lady built a bus Look.
Full of herbs, tortilla presses, buses,
Bible studies, Your Life in a Macaw.
Yeah. Oh, wow. Yeah.
Greek English literal translation, a
fancy one in the Layman's Bible
Encyclopedia.
>> I'll just give these away to anybody who
wants them.
Final haul. An entire bag of seeds, 72
packs of decaf coffee, gold mine
strainer, longo drum, about 50 lb of
different herbs and spices, whole bunch
of Bibles, an air pump, two copper cups,
tiny screwdriver set, a vacuum, a cool
copper pot, cast iron teapot, a grinding
pedestal, crowning achievement,
Mexican-made tortilla press. What do you
think the value of all this is? Like